Have you ever tried paw shoes? Because I got some silicone paw heels, shoes from Furjoy.
And if you don't know what I'm talking about, let me show you.
This is what I'm talking about.
So I posted a reel on Instagram with these, wearing these, and there were a lot of questions
and a lot of demands for a long YouTube video. So let's do this.
before I'm going to put them on I will tell you more about how they are built because
I had this question on Instagram too how much support and how much heel basically there is
because if you have a pony boot like you know them you know that there is a solid heel which
gives you a lot of support and you can't like wobble around on the shoe itself however with
these paw boots it is completely different because they don't have this kind of heel support they are
squishy and I can bend them I can twist them around the only thing that is really
hard is this bottom part here and other than that since it is so floppy you have to balance
yourself all the time and walk on your tiptoes so you walk on the ball of your
foot constantly on the inside there simply as they are on the outside it is
100% silicon through and through so 4 millimeter stretchy wobbly material okay
let's put them on you could use water-based lubricant and put that
inside to slip into them I would not do that for myself because I think it's too
slippery then if you like squishing around inside the shoe already and have
to balance so I put talcum powder inside and now let me see if it doesn't have to
right I don't think so and now I'm simply going to slip into them
and for the next one so with the amount of talcum powder I used
it's pretty easy you can already see it's white inside so I used a lot to get
inside really fast so I'm bunching them up here and putting my toes to the front
and then like tights putting them on now my heel is here where the thicker part
still is I'm having size 40 so shoe size UU 40 and this is how good they fit me
so it's basically perfect and my toes are here so they're in the front now my fingers are white
and this is what this looks like
now standing up and yes I'm instantly on my tiptoes so depending on your balance this
might be easier or harder for you. For me it's totally fine. And yeah, I can even like jump in
them doing all this on my tiptoes and I can already feel my calves kind of being exhausted
from walking on tiptoes constantly. So that's something you have to put into account as well.
it is basically exercise it's a workout to just move around like that and now here's the
philosophical question if this is silicone is this already a furry fetish because there's no fur
i don't know what do you think let me know in the comments and yeah
you can of course pair this with a full silicone catsuit from furjoy for example and mask and
build like a whole outfit and i do have a discount for furjoy i will link it in the
description text and write it down i'm constantly moving around because it's really easier
to stay upright in them if you're moving and if you're like not standing still because if
standing still then you really do have to balance on the spot which is harder.
All right I think this was a fun video I think they're kind of cute I hope you
enjoyed too so leave a thumbs up and a comment and check out my socials and the
discount code and I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!
Thank you.